{
	"description": "Kanji for 日本漢字能力検定 2級",
	"deck": [
	{ "question": "一献", "answers": [ "いっこん" ], "comment": "one cup (of sake)\n(going out for, treating someone to) a drink; small drinking party" },
	{ "question": "一矢", "answers": [ "いっし" ], "comment": "an arrow; (a) retort" },
	{ "question": "一蹴", "answers": [ "いっしゅう" ], "comment": "kicking\nrejecting; curtly refusing\ndefeating handily; winning easily" },
	{ "question": "丁寧", "answers": [ "ていねい" ], "comment": "polite; courteous; civil\ncareful; close; thorough; conscientious" },
	{ "question": "三角巾", "answers": [ "さんかくきん" ], "comment": "triangular bandage; sling\ntriangular kerchief; bandana; bandanna" },
	{ "question": "且つ", "answers": [ "かつ" ], "comment": "yet; moreover; and" },
	{ "question": "両脇", "answers": [ "りょうわき" ], "comment": "both sides" },
	{ "question": "丼勘定", "answers": [ "どんぶりかんじょう" ], "comment": "rough estimate; sloppy accounting; slapdash bookkeeping" },
	{ "question": "乞う", "answers": [ "こう" ], "comment": "to beg; to ask; to request; to invite" },
	{ "question": "乾麺", "answers": [ "かんめん" ], "comment": "dried noodles" },
	{ "question": "亀裂", "answers": [ "きれつ" ], "comment": "crack; crevice; fissure; chap; rift" },
	{ "question": "予鈴", "answers": [ "よれい" ], "comment": "bell signalling that work, class, etc. will formally begin shortly; first bell; warning bell" },
	{ "question": "亡者", "answers": [ "もうじゃ" ], "comment": "the dead" },
	{ "question": "付箋", "answers": [ "ふせん" ], "comment": "tag; slip; label" },
	{ "question": "会得", "answers": [ "えとく" ], "comment": "understanding; comprehension; grasp; perception; appreciation; mastery (of an art or skill)" },
	{ "question": "会釈", "answers": [ "えしゃく" ], "comment": "slight bow (as a greeting or sign of gratitude); nod; salutation\nconsideration; thoughtfulness" },
	{ "question": "伴い", "answers": [ "ともない" ], "comment": "companion; accompaniment" },
	{ "question": "伴侶", "answers": [ "はんりょ" ], "comment": "companion; partner; spouse" },
	{ "question": "但し", "answers": [ "ただし" ], "comment": "but; however; provided that" },
	{ "question": "侮る", "answers": [ "あなどる" ], "comment": "to disdain; to look down on; to make light of; to hold in contempt; to scorn; to despise" },
	{ "question": "侮れない", "answers": [ "あなどれない" ], "comment": "tough" },
	{ "question": "便箋", "answers": [ "びんせん" ], "comment": "writing paper; stationery" },
	{ "question": "促す", "answers": [ "うながす" ], "comment": "to urge; to press; to prompt; to suggest; to demand; to stimulate; to quicken; to incite; to invite (attention to)" },
	{ "question": "俊才", "answers": [ "しゅんさい" ], "comment": "prodigy; talented person; person of exceptional talent; genius" },
	{ "question": "俳諧", "answers": [ "はいかい" ], "comment": "haikai; collective name for haiku, haibun, haiga, senryū, etc.\nhumorous or vulgar renga poetry" },
	{ "question": "俺様", "answers": [ "おれさま" ], "comment": "I; myself" },
	{ "question": "倣う", "answers": [ "ならう" ], "comment": "to imitate; to follow; to emulate" },
	{ "question": "偏る", "answers": [ "かたよる" ], "comment": "to be one-sided; to incline; to be partial; to be prejudiced; to lean; to be biased; to be biassed" },
	{ "question": "偏狭", "answers": [ "へんきょう" ], "comment": "narrow-mindedness; intolerance; illiberality; narrowness" },
	{ "question": "偏窟", "answers": [ "へんくつ" ], "comment": "eccentricity; bigotry; obstinacy" },
	{ "question": "停頓", "answers": [ "ていとん" ], "comment": "deadlock; standstill; stalemate; set-back; abeyance" },
	{ "question": "偵察", "answers": [ "ていさつ" ], "comment": "scout out; reconnaissance" },
	{ "question": "偽", "answers": [ "にせ" ], "comment": "imitation; fake; phony; counterfeit; forged; bogus; sham\npseudo-\n(logic) false" },
	{ "question": "偽り", "answers": [ "いつわり" ], "comment": "lie; falsehood; fiction; fabrication" },
	{ "question": "傑作", "answers": [ "けっさく" ], "comment": "masterpiece; best work\namusing blunder; funny mistake; boner" },
	{ "question": "傑物", "answers": [ "けつぶつ" ], "comment": "great man; heroic figure; remarkable character" },
	{ "question": "傲岸", "answers": [ "ごうがん" ], "comment": "haughty; arrogant; supercilious" },
	{ "question": "傲慢", "answers": [ "ごうまん" ], "comment": "haughty; arrogant; insolent; proud; overbearing" },
	{ "question": "傲然", "answers": [ "ごうぜん" ], "comment": "proud; arrogant; haughty" },
	{ "question": "傲語", "answers": [ "ごうご" ] },
	{ "question": "僅か", "answers": [ "わずか" ], "comment": "only; merely; (a) little; small quantity" },
	{ "question": "僅少", "answers": [ "きんしょう" ], "comment": "(a) few; (a) little; trifling; insignificant; small (amount); scarce (stocks)" },
	{ "question": "僅差", "answers": [ "きんさ" ], "comment": "narrow margin (esp. victory or defeat); slim margin" },
	{ "question": "償う", "answers": [ "つぐなう" ], "comment": "to make up for; to compensate for; to indemnify; to recompense; to redeem (e.g. a fault); to atone for" },
	{ "question": "元旦", "answers": [ "がんたん" ], "comment": "New Year's Day\nNew Year's morning; morning of New Year's Day" },
	{ "question": "充填", "answers": [ "じゅうてん" ], "comment": "filling (up); replenishing; filling in (tooth); loading (gun with ammunition, camera with film, etc.); packing; plugging" },
	{ "question": "免れる", "answers": [ "まぬがれる", "まぬかれる" ], "comment": "to escape (disaster, death, etc.); to be saved from; to be rescued from\nto avoid (e.g. punishment); to evade (e.g. responsibility); to avert; to elude; to be exempted from" },
	{ "question": "免疫", "answers": [ "めんえき" ], "comment": "immunity; immunization; immunisation\nbeing hardened (to); being unaffected (by); being accustomed (to)" },
	{ "question": "全幅", "answers": [ "ぜんぷく" ], "comment": "full; wholehearted; utmost; all; every\noverall width" },
	{ "question": "八百長", "answers": [ "やおちょう" ], "comment": "match fixing; put-up job; fixed game" },
	{ "question": "冗談", "answers": [ "じょうだん" ], "comment": "jest; joke; funny story" },
	{ "question": "冥利", "answers": [ "みょうり" ], "comment": "providence; luck; favor; favour; advantage" },
	{ "question": "冥加", "answers": [ "みょうが" ], "comment": "divine protection or blessing" },
	{ "question": "冥土", "answers": [ "めいど" ], "comment": "Hades; the underworld; the other world; realm of the dead" },
	{ "question": "冶金学", "answers": [ "やきんがく" ], "comment": "metallurgy (the science)" },
	{ "question": "冷徹", "answers": [ "れいてつ" ], "comment": "cool-headed" },
	{ "question": "凄惨", "answers": [ "せいさん" ], "comment": "ghastly; gruesome; appalling; lurid" },
	{ "question": "凄然", "answers": [ "せいぜん" ] },
	{ "question": "凄艶", "answers": [ "せいえん" ], "comment": "weirdly beautiful" },
	{ "question": "凡例", "answers": [ "はんれい" ], "comment": "explanatory notes (at the start of a book); introductory remarks; usage guide (e.g. of a dictionary)\nlegend (on maps, drawings, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "処方箋", "answers": [ "しょほうせん" ], "comment": "prescription" },
	{ "question": "出藍", "answers": [ "しゅつらん" ], "comment": "pupil excelling his master" },
	{ "question": "利益", "answers": [ "りえき", "りやく" ], "comment": "profit; gains\nbenefit; advantage; interest (of the public, etc.)\ngrace (of God, Buddha, etc.) (esp. as attained through rightful actions, prayer, adherence to one's faith, etc.); blessing; miracle" },
	{ "question": "刹那", "answers": [ "せつな" ], "comment": "moment; instant; juncture" },
	{ "question": "剝がれる", "answers": [ "はがれる" ], "comment": "to come unstuck from; to peel off; to come off" },
	{ "question": "剥奪", "answers": [ "はくだつ" ], "comment": "deprivation; divestiture; revocation" },
	{ "question": "剥製", "answers": [ "はくせい" ], "comment": "stuffing; mounting\nstuffed animal" },
	{ "question": "剥離", "answers": [ "はくり" ], "comment": "detachment; coming off; peeling off\nseparation" },
	{ "question": "励ます", "answers": [ "はげます" ], "comment": "to encourage; to cheer; to raise (the voice)" },
	{ "question": "勃発", "answers": [ "ぼっぱつ" ], "comment": "outbreak (e.g. war); outburst; sudden occurrence" },
	{ "question": "勃興", "answers": [ "ぼっこう" ], "comment": "sudden rise to power; sudden rise in prosperity" },
	{ "question": "勲章", "answers": [ "くんしょう" ], "comment": "decoration; order; medal" },
	{ "question": "勾留", "answers": [ "こうりゅう" ], "comment": "detention pending trial; confinement; custody" },
	{ "question": "勾配", "answers": [ "こうばい" ], "comment": "slope; incline; gradient; grade; pitch\nslope (of a linear function)\ngradient (vector calculus)" },
	{ "question": "匂い", "answers": [ "におい" ], "comment": "odour; odor; scent; smell; stench\naura; whiff; smacks of ...; sense; flavour; flavor" },
	{ "question": "化粧", "answers": [ "けしょう" ], "comment": "make-up; makeup; cosmetics" },
	{ "question": "匿名", "answers": [ "とくめい" ], "comment": "anonymity; using an assumed name" },
	{ "question": "千羽鶴", "answers": [ "せんばづる" ], "comment": "(string of) many (traditionally 1000) paper cranes" },
	{ "question": "卑下", "answers": [ "ひげ" ], "comment": "self-abasement; humility; self-depreciation" },
	{ "question": "危惧", "answers": [ "きぐ" ], "comment": "apprehensions; misgivings; uneasiness; anxiety; fear" },
	{ "question": "厳粛", "answers": [ "げんしゅく" ], "comment": "gravity; solemnity; severity; seriousness; dignity; rigor; rigour; austerity" },
	{ "question": "双子", "answers": [ "ふたご" ], "comment": "twins; twin" },
	{ "question": "双璧", "answers": [ "そうへき" ], "comment": "(two) matchless things; (two) matchless people\npair of bright jewels" },
	{ "question": "反物", "answers": [ "たんもの" ], "comment": "fabric; cloth; textiles; drapery; dry-goods; piece goods\nmeasure of kimono material" },
	{ "question": "古刹", "answers": [ "こさつ" ], "comment": "ancient temple" },
	{ "question": "叱る", "answers": [ "しかる" ], "comment": "to scold; to chide; to rebuke; to reprimand" },
	{ "question": "叱声", "answers": [ "しっせい" ], "comment": "scolding voice" },
	{ "question": "叱正", "answers": [ "しっせい" ], "comment": "pointing out errors; correction; critique" },
	{ "question": "叱責", "answers": [ "しっせき" ], "comment": "reprimand; rebuke" },
	{ "question": "右舷", "answers": [ "うげん" ], "comment": "starboard" },
	{ "question": "否めない", "answers": [ "いなめない" ], "comment": "cannot deny; undeniable; incontrovertible" },
	{ "question": "含羞", "answers": [ "がんしゅう" ], "comment": "shyness\nbashfulness; shyness; (showing) signs of embarrassment" },
	{ "question": "呪文", "answers": [ "じゅもん" ], "comment": "spell; charm; incantation; magic word" },
	{ "question": "呪縛", "answers": [ "じゅばく" ], "comment": "curse; spell" },
	{ "question": "命乞い", "answers": [ "いのちごい" ], "comment": "begging for one's life; pleading for one's life" },
	{ "question": "和睦", "answers": [ "わぼく" ], "comment": "reconciliation; peace; rapprochement" },
	{ "question": "咽喉", "answers": [ "いんこう" ], "comment": "throat" },
	{ "question": "哀悼", "answers": [ "あいとう" ], "comment": "condolence; regret; tribute; sorrow; sympathy; lament" },
	{ "question": "哀愁", "answers": [ "あいしゅう" ], "comment": "pathos; sorrow; grief" },
	{ "question": "哲学", "answers": [ "てつがく" ], "comment": "philosophy" },
	{ "question": "哺乳瓶", "answers": [ "ほにゅうびん" ], "comment": "baby bottle" },
	{ "question": "唆す", "answers": [ "そそのかす" ], "comment": "to instigate; to tempt" },
	{ "question": "唇", "answers": [ "くちびる" ], "comment": "lips" },
	{ "question": "唯一", "answers": [ "ゆいいつ" ], "comment": "only; sole; unique" },
	{ "question": "唾棄", "answers": [ "だき" ], "comment": "despising; disdaining; scorning; holding in contempt" },
	{ "question": "喉元", "answers": [ "のどもと" ], "comment": "throat" },
	{ "question": "喝破", "answers": [ "かっぱ" ], "comment": "arguing someone down; scolding; rebuking\nproclaiming (the truth); expounding" },
	{ "question": "喝采", "answers": [ "かっさい" ], "comment": "acclamation; applause; ovation; cheers" },
	{ "question": "喪失", "answers": [ "そうしつ" ], "comment": "loss; forfeit" },
	{ "question": "営巣", "answers": [ "えいそう" ], "comment": "building a nest" },
	{ "question": "嗅ぐ", "answers": [ "かぐ" ], "comment": "to sniff; to smell" },
	{ "question": "嗅覚", "answers": [ "きゅうかく" ], "comment": "sense of smell; olfaction" },
	{ "question": "嘲る", "answers": [ "あざける" ], "comment": "to scoff; to laugh at; to make fun of; to ridicule; to jeer at" },
	{ "question": "嘲弄", "answers": [ "ちょうろう" ], "comment": "scorn; mockery; ridicule" },
	{ "question": "嘲笑", "answers": [ "ちょうしょう" ], "comment": "scorn; sneer" },
	{ "question": "嘲罵", "answers": [ "ちょうば" ], "comment": "taunt; insult; abuse" },
	{ "question": "回向", "answers": [ "えこう" ], "comment": "Buddhist memorial service; prayers for the repose of the soul" },
	{ "question": "国璽", "answers": [ "こくじ" ], "comment": "the seal of state" },
	{ "question": "土壇場", "answers": [ "どたんば" ], "comment": "last moment; eleventh hour\nplatform made of dirt used to perform executions (decapitations) in the Edo period" },
	{ "question": "土壌", "answers": [ "どじょう" ], "comment": "soil\nbreeding ground; fertile ground (for); foundation (for the development of ...)" },
	{ "question": "土産", "answers": [ "みやげ" ], "comment": "present; souvenir\nproduct of the land\npresent; souvenir" },
	{ "question": "地下茎", "answers": [ "ちかけい" ], "comment": "rhizome" },
	{ "question": "均斉", "answers": [ "きんせい" ], "comment": "symmetry; balance; proportion; uniformity" },
	{ "question": "埋葬", "answers": [ "まいそう" ], "comment": "burial" },
	{ "question": "執念", "answers": [ "しゅうねん" ], "comment": "tenacity; persistence; obsession; implacability" },
	{ "question": "培う", "answers": [ "つちかう" ], "comment": "to cultivate; to foster" },
	{ "question": "堆積", "answers": [ "たいせき" ], "comment": "accumulation; pile; heap\nsedimentation" },
	{ "question": "堆肥", "answers": [ "たいひ" ], "comment": "compost" },
	{ "question": "堕落", "answers": [ "だらく" ], "comment": "depravity; corruption; degradation" },
	{ "question": "塞がる", "answers": [ "ふさがる" ], "comment": "to be closed; to be blocked; to be healed (e.g. wound); to be shut up\nto be clogged; to be plugged up\nto be occupied; to be taken (e.g. accommodation)" },
	{ "question": "塞ぐ", "answers": [ "ふさぐ" ], "comment": "to stop up; to close up; to block (up); to plug up; to shut up; to cover (ears, eyes, etc.); to close (eyes, mouth)\nto stand in the way; to obstruct\nto occupy; to fill up; to take up\nto perform one's role; to do one's duty\nto feel depressed; to mope" },
	{ "question": "壮図", "answers": [ "そうと" ], "comment": "ambitious undertaking; grand scheme" },
	{ "question": "変貌", "answers": [ "へんぼう" ], "comment": "transfiguration; transformation; change of appearance" },
	{ "question": "夕闇", "answers": [ "ゆうやみ" ], "comment": "dusk; twilight" },
	{ "question": "夢枕", "answers": [ "ゆめまくら" ], "comment": "at the bedside where one dreams" },
	{ "question": "大尉", "answers": [ "たいい" ], "comment": "captain (Army, U.S. Marine Corps, USAF); lieutenant (Navy); flight lieutenant (RAF, RAAF, RNZAF, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "大胆", "answers": [ "だいたん" ], "comment": "bold; daring; audacious" },
	{ "question": "失跡", "answers": [ "しっせき" ], "comment": "absconding; disappearance" },
	{ "question": "失踪", "answers": [ "しっそう" ], "comment": "absconding; disappearance" },
	{ "question": "奈落", "answers": [ "ならく" ], "comment": "Naraka; hell; hades\nvery bottom; the end; worst possible circumstances\ntheatre basement; theater basement" },
	{ "question": "奔走", "answers": [ "ほんそう" ], "comment": "running about; making every effort; being busily engaged (in something); good offices" },
	{ "question": "好事家", "answers": [ "こうずか" ], "comment": "dilettante; person of fantastic taste" },
	{ "question": "好餌", "answers": [ "こうじ" ], "comment": "bait; decoy; lure\neasy prey; easy victim; sucker" },
	{ "question": "妖しい", "answers": [ "あやしい" ], "comment": "charming; bewitching; mysterious" },
	{ "question": "妖艶", "answers": [ "ようえん" ], "comment": "fascinating; voluptuous; bewitching" },
	{ "question": "妥協", "answers": [ "だきょう" ], "comment": "compromise; giving in" },
	{ "question": "妨げる", "answers": [ "さまたげる" ], "comment": "to disturb; to prevent; to obstruct; to hinder" },
	{ "question": "妨害", "answers": [ "ぼうがい" ], "comment": "disturbance; obstruction; hindrance; jamming; interference" },
	{ "question": "妬む", "answers": [ "ねたむ" ], "comment": "to be jealous of; to envy; to begrudge" },
	{ "question": "姻戚", "answers": [ "いんせき" ], "comment": "relative by marriage; affinity" },
	{ "question": "威嚇", "answers": [ "いかく" ], "comment": "menace; threat; intimidation\nto threaten; to intimidate" },
	{ "question": "媒酌", "answers": [ "ばいしゃく" ], "comment": "matchmaking" },
	{ "question": "嫉妬", "answers": [ "しっと" ], "comment": "jealousy; envy" },
	{ "question": "嫉視", "answers": [ "しっし" ], "comment": "jealousy\nto be jealous" },
	{ "question": "嫌悪", "answers": [ "けんお" ], "comment": "disgust; hate; repugnance" },
	{ "question": "嫡子", "answers": [ "ちゃくし" ], "comment": "legitimate child" },
	{ "question": "孤立", "answers": [ "こりつ" ], "comment": "isolation; being alone; being friendless" },
	{ "question": "安寧", "answers": [ "あんねい" ], "comment": "peace (esp. public peace)" },
	{ "question": "安泰", "answers": [ "あんたい" ], "comment": "peace; security; tranquility; tranquillity" },
	{ "question": "完璧", "answers": [ "かんぺき" ], "comment": "perfect; complete; flawless" },
	{ "question": "宛てる", "answers": [ "あてる" ], "comment": "to address" },
	{ "question": "宛先", "answers": [ "あてさき" ], "comment": "address; destination" },
	{ "question": "宰領", "answers": [ "さいりょう" ], "comment": "supervision; superintendence; management; supervisor" },
	{ "question": "寄席", "answers": [ "よせ" ], "comment": "entertainment hall (for rakugo, manzai, magic, music, etc.); vaudeville theater (theatre); music hall" },
	{ "question": "富裕", "answers": [ "ふゆう" ], "comment": "wealth; riches; opulence" },
	{ "question": "寛大", "answers": [ "かんだい" ], "comment": "tolerant; generous; lenient; broad-minded; magnanimous" },
	{ "question": "寡聞", "answers": [ "かぶん" ], "comment": "limited information" },
	{ "question": "寡黙", "answers": [ "かもく" ], "comment": "silent (person); shy; taciturn; reticent; uncommunicative" },
	{ "question": "寸隙", "answers": [ "すんげき" ], "comment": "spare time; spare moment\nsmall opening; small crack" },
	{ "question": "尊崇", "answers": [ "そんすう" ], "comment": "reverence; veneration" },
	{ "question": "尚早", "answers": [ "しょうそう" ], "comment": "prematurity" },
	{ "question": "尻拭い", "answers": [ "しりぬぐい" ], "comment": "cleaning up or covering for another; bearing the consequences of someone else's error; paying a debt for someone; wiping another's buttocks" },
	{ "question": "尻餅", "answers": [ "しりもち" ], "comment": "falling on one's backside (behind, bottom); pratfall\nmochi used to celebrate a child's first birthday; mochi tied to a baby's back if he starts walking before his first birthday in order to cause him to fall on his backside" },
	{ "question": "屈託", "answers": [ "くったく" ], "comment": "worry; care; concern\nennui; boredom" },
	{ "question": "履行", "answers": [ "りこう" ], "comment": "performance; fulfillment; fulfilment; discharge; implementation" },
	{ "question": "山麓", "answers": [ "さんろく" ], "comment": "foot of a mountain; base of a mountain" },
	{ "question": "岩窟", "answers": [ "がんくつ" ], "comment": "cave; cavern" },
	{ "question": "岬", "answers": [ "みさき" ], "comment": "small peninsula\ncape (on coast)" },
	{ "question": "崇高", "answers": [ "すうこう" ], "comment": "lofty; sublime; noble\nthe sublime (aesthetics)" },
	{ "question": "崖", "answers": [ "がけ" ], "comment": "cliff" },
	{ "question": "崖下", "answers": [ "がいか" ], "comment": "below a cliff" },
	{ "question": "巣窟", "answers": [ "そうくつ" ], "comment": "den; haunt; hangout; home" },
	{ "question": "巧緻", "answers": [ "こうち" ], "comment": "elaborate; exquisite; detailed" },
	{ "question": "巾着", "answers": [ "きんちゃく" ], "comment": "drawstring purse; money pouch\npouch of fried tofu stuffed with var. ingredients, used in oden\nunlicensed prostitute (Edo period)" },
	{ "question": "布施", "answers": [ "ふせ" ], "comment": "alms; offerings" },
	{ "question": "平癒", "answers": [ "へいゆ" ], "comment": "recovery; convalescence" },
	{ "question": "年俸", "answers": [ "ねんぽう" ], "comment": "annual salary" },
	{ "question": "年端", "answers": [ "としは" ], "comment": "age; years (old)" },
	{ "question": "庶務課", "answers": [ "しょむか" ], "comment": "general affairs section" },
	{ "question": "廃れる", "answers": [ "すたれる" ], "comment": "to go out of use; to become obsolete; to die out; to go out of fashion" },
	{ "question": "廃屋", "answers": [ "はいおく" ], "comment": "dilapidated house; deserted house" },
	{ "question": "弊害", "answers": [ "へいがい" ], "comment": "harmful effect; harmful influence; evil practice; abuse; malady" },
	{ "question": "弊社", "answers": [ "へいしゃ" ], "comment": "our firm; our company" },
	{ "question": "弔う", "answers": [ "とむらう" ], "comment": "to mourn for; to condole with (family, etc.)\nto hold a memorial service (for)" },
	{ "question": "弔電", "answers": [ "ちょうでん" ], "comment": "telegram of condolence" },
	{ "question": "弥次馬", "answers": [ "やじうま" ], "comment": "curious onlookers; rubbernecks" },
	{ "question": "弥生", "answers": [ "やよい" ], "comment": "third month of the lunar calendar\nthick growth (of grass, etc.)\nYayoi period (ca. 300 BCE - 300 CE)" },
	{ "question": "彙報", "answers": [ "いほう" ], "comment": "bulletin; collection of reports" },
	{ "question": "形骸化", "answers": [ "けいがいか" ], "comment": "becoming a mere shell; becoming a dead letter; losing (one's) substance; being reduced to a formality" },
	{ "question": "往詣", "answers": [ "おうけい" ] },
	{ "question": "待遇", "answers": [ "たいぐう" ], "comment": "treatment; reception; service\nworking conditions; salary; pay; remuneration" },
	{ "question": "従容", "answers": [ "しょうよう" ], "comment": "calm; composed; tranquil" },
	{ "question": "御法度", "answers": [ "ごはっと" ], "comment": "contraband; taboo; strictly forbidden" },
	{ "question": "循環", "answers": [ "じゅんかん" ], "comment": "circulation; rotation; cycle" },
	{ "question": "必須", "answers": [ "ひっす" ], "comment": "indispensable; required" },
	{ "question": "忍ばせる", "answers": [ "しのばせる" ], "comment": "to conceal; to hide" },
	{ "question": "思索", "answers": [ "しさく" ], "comment": "speculation; thinking; meditation" },
	{ "question": "怠ける", "answers": [ "なまける" ], "comment": "to be idle; to slacken\nto neglect (e.g. one's work)" },
	{ "question": "急騰", "answers": [ "きゅうとう" ], "comment": "sudden rise; jump; sharp rise" },
	{ "question": "怨念", "answers": [ "おんねん" ], "comment": "grudge; malice; hatred" },
	{ "question": "怨恨", "answers": [ "えんこん" ], "comment": "enmity; grudge" },
	{ "question": "怨霊", "answers": [ "おんりょう" ], "comment": "revengeful ghost; apparition" },
	{ "question": "恐竜", "answers": [ "きょうりゅう" ], "comment": "dinosaur" },
	{ "question": "恣意", "answers": [ "しい" ], "comment": "arbitrariness" },
	{ "question": "恣行", "answers": [ "しこう" ] },
	{ "question": "恩恵", "answers": [ "おんけい" ], "comment": "grace; favor; favour; blessing; benefit" },
	{ "question": "恭しい", "answers": [ "うやうやしい" ], "comment": "respectful; reverent" },
	{ "question": "悠長", "answers": [ "ゆうちょう" ], "comment": "leisurely; slow; deliberate; easygoing" },
	{ "question": "悪寒", "answers": [ "おかん" ], "comment": "chill; shakes; ague" },
	{ "question": "悼む", "answers": [ "いたむ" ], "comment": "to grieve over; to mourn; to lament" },
	{ "question": "惜しくも", "answers": [ "おしくも" ], "comment": "to one's regret; regrettably; to one's chagrin" },
	{ "question": "惨禍", "answers": [ "さんか" ], "comment": "calamity" },
	{ "question": "愁嘆場", "answers": [ "しゅうたんば" ], "comment": "pathetic scene" },
	{ "question": "意気地無し", "answers": [ "いくじなし" ], "comment": "coward; timid creature" },
	{ "question": "愚か", "answers": [ "おろか" ], "comment": "foolish; stupid" },
	{ "question": "愚弄", "answers": [ "ぐろう" ], "comment": "mockery; derision; ridicule" },
	{ "question": "愚昧", "answers": [ "ぐまい" ], "comment": "stupid" },
	{ "question": "愚痴", "answers": [ "ぐち" ], "comment": "idle complaint; grumble\nmoha (ignorance, folly)" },
	{ "question": "愛媛県", "answers": [ "えひめけん" ], "comment": "Ehime prefecture (Shikoku)" },
	{ "question": "愛嬌", "answers": [ "あいきょう" ], "comment": "charm; attractiveness; amiability; winsomeness\ncourtesy; ingratiating behaviour\nentertainment; amusement; fun" },
	{ "question": "愛猫", "answers": [ "あいびょう" ], "comment": "pet cat; beloved cat\nailurophilia; fondness for cats" },
	{ "question": "愛玩", "answers": [ "あいがん" ], "comment": "caring for (esp. a pet or a small object); cherishing; being fond of; prizing; treasuring" },
	{ "question": "慄然", "answers": [ "りつぜん" ], "comment": "terrified; horrified" },
	{ "question": "慌てる", "answers": [ "あわてる" ], "comment": "to become confused (disconcerted, disorganized, disorganised); to be flustered; to panic\nto be in a hurry; to rush" },
	{ "question": "慰める", "answers": [ "なぐさめる" ], "comment": "to comfort; to console; to amuse" },
	{ "question": "慶事", "answers": [ "けいじ" ], "comment": "auspicious event" },
	{ "question": "憂う", "answers": [ "うれう" ], "comment": "to worry; to be concerned\nto grieve; to lament; to be anxious; to be distressed" },
	{ "question": "憂惧", "answers": [ "ゆうぐ" ] },
	{ "question": "憤り", "answers": [ "いきどおり" ], "comment": "resentment; indignation; anger" },
	{ "question": "憤る", "answers": [ "いきどおる" ], "comment": "to be angry; to resent; to be enraged; to be indignant\nto fret; to be fretful; to be peevish" },
	{ "question": "憤怒", "answers": [ "ふんど", "ふんぬ" ], "comment": "anger; rage; resentment; indignation; exasperation" },
	{ "question": "憧れる", "answers": [ "あこがれる" ], "comment": "to long for; to yearn after; to admire; to be attracted by" },
	{ "question": "憧憬", "answers": [ "しょうけい", "どうけい" ], "comment": "longing; aspiration" },
	{ "question": "懇々", "answers": [ "こんこん" ], "comment": "repeated; earnest; kind" },
	{ "question": "懇ろ", "answers": [ "ねんごろ" ], "comment": "kind; courteous; hospitable; warmly respectful\nintimate\nbecoming intimate; having an intimate relationship (sometimes esp. a homosexual relationship)" },
	{ "question": "懐", "answers": [ "ふところ" ], "comment": "bosom; bust\n(breast) pocket; purse; handbag" },
	{ "question": "懐かしい", "answers": [ "なつかしい" ], "comment": "dear; desired; missed" },
	{ "question": "懐柔", "answers": [ "かいじゅう" ], "comment": "winning over; placation; gentle persuasion" },
	{ "question": "懲らしめる", "answers": [ "こらしめる" ], "comment": "to chastise; to punish; to discipline" },
	{ "question": "懲りずに", "answers": [ "こりずに" ] },
	{ "question": "懸念", "answers": [ "けねん" ], "comment": "worry; fear; anxiety; concern" },
	{ "question": "成就", "answers": [ "じょうじゅ" ], "comment": "fulfillment; fulfilment; realization; realisation; completion" },
	{ "question": "戦慄", "answers": [ "せんりつ" ], "comment": "shudder; shiver; trembling with fear" },
	{ "question": "戴冠", "answers": [ "たいかん" ], "comment": "coronation; crowning" },
	{ "question": "所詮", "answers": [ "しょせん" ], "comment": "after all" },
	{ "question": "手綱", "answers": [ "たづな" ], "comment": "bridle; reins" },
	{ "question": "手頃", "answers": [ "てごろ" ], "comment": "moderate; handy; convenient; reasonable" },
	{ "question": "才媛", "answers": [ "さいえん" ], "comment": "literary woman; talented woman" },
	{ "question": "払拭", "answers": [ "ふっしょく" ], "comment": "wiping out; sweeping away" },
	{ "question": "払暁", "answers": [ "ふつぎょう" ], "comment": "dawn; daybreak" },
	{ "question": "抄訳", "answers": [ "しょうやく" ], "comment": "abridged translation" },
	{ "question": "抑える", "answers": [ "おさえる" ], "comment": "to pin something down; to hold something down; to hold something back; to stop; to restrain; to curb\nto seize; to grasp; to arrest\nto gain control of something; to govern; to keep down (e.g. information); to suppress\nto catch happening; to determine (important points); to find (proof); to understand" },
	{ "question": "担う", "answers": [ "になう" ], "comment": "to carry on shoulder; to shoulder (gun)\nto bear (burden, responsibility, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "拉致", "answers": [ "らち" ], "comment": "taking captive; carrying away; kidnapping; kidnaping; abduction" },
	{ "question": "拒む", "answers": [ "こばむ" ], "comment": "to refuse; to reject; to decline" },
	{ "question": "拒否", "answers": [ "きょひ" ], "comment": "denial; veto; rejection; refusal" },
	{ "question": "拘泥", "answers": [ "こうでい" ], "comment": "adhering to; being a stickler for; being particular about; worrying too much about" },
	{ "question": "拙宅", "answers": [ "せったく" ], "comment": "one's home; one's humble abode" },
	{ "question": "拝謁", "answers": [ "はいえつ" ], "comment": "having an audience with someone of very high social standing (e.g. the emperor)" },
	{ "question": "拭う", "answers": [ "ぬぐう" ], "comment": "to wipe\nto get rid of; to eliminate (e.g. one's shame); to remove (e.g. an impression); to erase" },
	{ "question": "拭浄", "answers": [ "しょくじょう" ], "comment": "wiping and purifying; wiping and cleansing" },
	{ "question": "拳銃", "answers": [ "けんじゅう" ], "comment": "pistol; handgun; revolver" },
	{ "question": "挟まる", "answers": [ "はさまる" ], "comment": "to get between; to be caught in" },
	{ "question": "挨拶", "answers": [ "あいさつ" ], "comment": "greeting; greetings; salutation; salute; polite set phrase used when meeting or parting from somebody\npolite set phrase used to express apology, sympathy, congratulations, etc.\nspeech (congratulatory or appreciative); address\nreply; response\nrevenge; retaliation\na fine thing to say (used as part of a sarcastic response to a rude remark)\ndialoging (with another Zen practitioner to ascertain their level of enlightenment)\nrelationship (between people); connection\nintervention; mediation; mediator" },
	{ "question": "挫折", "answers": [ "ざせつ" ], "comment": "setback; failure (e.g. plans, business); frustration; discouragement" },
	{ "question": "捉える", "answers": [ "とらえる" ], "comment": "to catch; to capture; to seize; to arrest; to grab; to catch hold of\nto grasp (e.g. meaning); to perceive; to capture (e.g. features)\nto captivate; to move (one's heart)" },
	{ "question": "捕捉", "answers": [ "ほそく" ], "comment": "capture; seizure; prehension; trapping\napprehension; understanding; grasp" },
	{ "question": "据える", "answers": [ "すえる" ], "comment": "to place (in position); to fix; to set (e.g. table); to lay (foundation)\nto install; to seat (someone)\nto settle (upon something); to fix (e.g. one's gaze)\nto apply (moxa)" },
	{ "question": "捻出", "answers": [ "ねんしゅつ" ], "comment": "contriving (to raise funds, to find time, etc.)\nworking out (a solution)" },
	{ "question": "捻挫", "answers": [ "ねんざ" ], "comment": "sprain" },
	{ "question": "掃除", "answers": [ "そうじ" ], "comment": "cleaning; sweeping; dusting; scrubbing" },
	{ "question": "排斥", "answers": [ "はいせき" ], "comment": "rejection; expulsion; boycott; ostracism" },
	{ "question": "接舷", "answers": [ "せつげん" ], "comment": "coming alongside (a boat, pier, etc)" },
	{ "question": "掲載", "answers": [ "けいさい" ], "comment": "publication (e.g. article in paper); appearance; insertion\nto insert (e.g. an article); to run (e.g. in a newspaper); to carry (e.g. an article); to post (e.g. on the Web)" },
	{ "question": "提携", "answers": [ "ていけい" ], "comment": "cooperation; tie-up; joint business; link-up; sponsorship" },
	{ "question": "揺れる", "answers": [ "ゆれる" ], "comment": "to shake; to sway; to waver" },
	{ "question": "搭載", "answers": [ "とうさい" ], "comment": "loading (on board); equipping\nequipped (with); built-in" },
	{ "question": "摂取", "answers": [ "せっしゅ" ], "comment": "intake; absorption; adoption\nassimilation" },
	{ "question": "摯実", "answers": [ "しじつ" ], "comment": "serious, sincere" },
	{ "question": "撤回", "answers": [ "てっかい" ], "comment": "withdrawal; retraction; revocation; repeal" },
	{ "question": "撮影", "answers": [ "さつえい" ], "comment": "photography (still or motion); photographing; filming; shooting; (video) recording" },
	{ "question": "撲滅", "answers": [ "ぼくめつ" ], "comment": "eradication; extermination; destruction; suppression" },
	{ "question": "擁護", "answers": [ "ようご" ], "comment": "protection; advocacy; support; defence; championship; vindication\nto protect (e.g. rights, etc.); to advocate (e.g. free trade, etc.); to support" },
	{ "question": "放恣", "answers": [ "ほうし" ], "comment": "licentious; self-indulgent" },
	{ "question": "散逸", "answers": [ "さんいつ" ], "comment": "being scattered and ultimately lost\ndissipation" },
	{ "question": "整頓", "answers": [ "せいとん" ], "comment": "orderliness; put in order; tidying up; arranging neatly" },
	{ "question": "斎場", "answers": [ "さいじょう" ], "comment": "funeral hall\nceremony site" },
	{ "question": "斑点", "answers": [ "はんてん" ], "comment": "speck; fleck" },
	{ "question": "斑紋", "answers": [ "はんもん" ], "comment": "speckles; spotted pattern" },
	{ "question": "斬撃", "answers": [ "ざんげき" ], "comment": "slash; slashing attack" },
	{ "question": "斬新", "answers": [ "ざんしん" ], "comment": "novel; original; newness" },
	{ "question": "断崖", "answers": [ "だんがい" ], "comment": "palisade; cliff" },
	{ "question": "施主", "answers": [ "せしゅ" ], "comment": "donor; benefactor; almsgiver\nchief mourner\nclient (of a builder, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "施錠", "answers": [ "せじょう" ], "comment": "locking" },
	{ "question": "旋回", "answers": [ "せんかい" ], "comment": "revolution; rotation; turning; circling; swiveling\nturning (an aircraft or ship)" },
	{ "question": "旋風", "answers": [ "せんぷう" ], "comment": "whirlwind\ncommotion; sensation; hullabaloo" },
	{ "question": "既に", "answers": [ "すでに" ], "comment": "already; too late" },
	{ "question": "旦夕", "answers": [ "たんせき" ], "comment": "on the brink of\nmorning and evening; day and night" },
	{ "question": "旨", "answers": [ "むね" ], "comment": "principle; aim; main purpose; central part; pillar\npurport; gist; drift; meaning\ninstructions; orders; intention; wishes" },
	{ "question": "旺然", "answers": [ "おうぜん" ], "comment": "prosperous" },
	{ "question": "旺盛", "answers": [ "おうせい" ], "comment": "full of vim and vigor" },
	{ "question": "明瞭", "answers": [ "めいりょう" ], "comment": "clarity; clearness" },
	{ "question": "時宜", "answers": [ "じぎ" ], "comment": "right time; appropriate time; season's greetings" },
	{ "question": "曖昧", "answers": [ "あいまい" ], "comment": "vague; ambiguous; unclear\nfuzzy" },
	{ "question": "更迭", "answers": [ "こうてつ" ], "comment": "change; shake-up; reshuffle (e.g. of a cabinet); dismissal (e.g. of a minister); exchanging places" },
	{ "question": "書棚", "answers": [ "しょだな" ], "comment": "bookshelf" },
	{ "question": "木琴", "answers": [ "もっきん" ], "comment": "xylophone" },
	{ "question": "未曽有", "answers": [ "みぞう" ], "comment": "unprecedented; unheard of" },
	{ "question": "本棚", "answers": [ "ほんだな" ], "comment": "bookshelves; bookshelf; bookcase" },
	{ "question": "来賓", "answers": [ "らいひん" ], "comment": "guest; visitor; visitor's arrival" },
	{ "question": "枝垂れ", "answers": [ "しだれ" ], "comment": "weeping form (e.g. tree)" },
	{ "question": "枯渇", "answers": [ "こかつ" ], "comment": "drying up; becoming exhausted; running dry; starvation" },
	{ "question": "架空", "answers": [ "かくう" ], "comment": "aerial; overhead\nfictitious; imaginary; fanciful; fabricated" },
	{ "question": "柿", "answers": [ "かき" ], "comment": "kaki; Japanese persimmon (Diospyros kaki)\nchopped wood; wood chips\nthin shingles" },
	{ "question": "核心", "answers": [ "かくしん" ], "comment": "core; heart (of the matter); point; crux; kernel" },
	{ "question": "桁違い", "answers": [ "けたちがい" ], "comment": "an order of magnitude higher; off by a digit; in a different league; unbelievable; incomparable; unimaginable" },
	{ "question": "梗概", "answers": [ "こうがい" ], "comment": "outline; summary; epitome" },
	{ "question": "梨", "answers": [ "なし" ], "comment": "nashi (Pyrus pyrifolia, esp. var. culta); Japanese pear; Asian pear; sand pear; apple pear" },
	{ "question": "棚", "answers": [ "たな" ], "comment": "shelf; shelves; ledge; rack\ntrellis" },
	{ "question": "椅子", "answers": [ "いす" ], "comment": "chair; stool\npost; office; position\ntraditional square chair with armrests and a torii-shaped back (used by the emperor, etc. during ceremonies)" },
	{ "question": "椎間板", "answers": [ "ついかんばん" ], "comment": "intervertebral disk" },
	{ "question": "楷書体", "answers": [ "かいしょたい" ], "comment": "square (block) style of printed typeface" },
	{ "question": "楽譜", "answers": [ "がくふ" ], "comment": "score; sheet music" },
	{ "question": "模索", "answers": [ "もさく" ], "comment": "groping (for); exploring for a solution" },
	{ "question": "横柄", "answers": [ "おうへい" ], "comment": "arrogant; haughty; insolent" },
	{ "question": "欺く", "answers": [ "あざむく" ], "comment": "to deceive; to delude; to trick; to fool\nto be as ... as ... (e.g. \"as bright as day\", \"as beautiful as a rose\")" },
	{ "question": "歌舞伎", "answers": [ "かぶき" ], "comment": "kabuki; Japanese classical drama" },
	{ "question": "殉職", "answers": [ "じゅんしょく" ], "comment": "dying at one's post; being killed in the line of duty" },
	{ "question": "殊勝", "answers": [ "しゅしょう" ], "comment": "admirable; laudable" },
	{ "question": "残骸", "answers": [ "ざんがい" ], "comment": "ruins; wreckage" },
	{ "question": "殻", "answers": [ "から" ], "comment": "shell; husk; hull; pod; chaff\nchicken bones (e.g. for soup); chicken carcass\npoor-quality coke (coal)\nleft-overs; remnants\nshell (e.g. electron shell)\negg; eggshell" },
	{ "question": "毀傷", "answers": [ "きしょう" ], "comment": "injury; damage" },
	{ "question": "毀損", "answers": [ "きそん" ], "comment": "damage; injury; defamation; waste" },
	{ "question": "毀棄", "answers": [ "きき" ], "comment": "destruction; demolition; damage" },
	{ "question": "毀誉", "answers": [ "きよ" ], "comment": "praise and censure; approval and disapproval; approbation and condemnation" },
	{ "question": "比喩", "answers": [ "ひゆ" ], "comment": "simile; metaphor; allegory; parable" },
	{ "question": "比肩", "answers": [ "ひけん" ], "comment": "ranking equal with; comparing favourably with; comparing favorably with" },
	{ "question": "氾濫", "answers": [ "はんらん" ], "comment": "overflowing; flood; inundation; deluge\noversupply; plethora" },
	{ "question": "汎用性", "answers": [ "はんようせい" ], "comment": "versatility; multiplicity of use" },
	{ "question": "汎説", "answers": [ "はんせつ" ] },
	{ "question": "沃野", "answers": [ "よくや" ], "comment": "fertile fields or plain" },
	{ "question": "沙汰", "answers": [ "さた" ], "comment": "affair; state; incident; issue; matter\nverdict; sentence\ndirections; orders; command; instructions\nnotice; information; communication; news; message; tidings; update" },
	{ "question": "波止場", "answers": [ "はとば" ], "comment": "wharf; quay; landing-stage; jetty" },
	{ "question": "泥縄", "answers": [ "どろなわ" ], "comment": "measure taken too late; measure taken in haste" },
	{ "question": "泰然", "answers": [ "たいぜん" ], "comment": "calm; composed; self-possessed; firm" },
	{ "question": "洞窟", "answers": [ "どうくつ" ], "comment": "cavern; cave; cave system; grotto" },
	{ "question": "浄瑠璃", "answers": [ "じょうるり" ], "comment": "type of dramatic recitation accompanied by a shamisen (associated with the Japanese puppet theater)" },
	{ "question": "涙腺", "answers": [ "るいせん" ], "comment": "tear gland; lacrimal gland" },
	{ "question": "涼しい", "answers": [ "すずしい" ], "comment": "cool; refreshing\nclear (e.g. eyes); bright\nclear; distinct\ncomposed (facial expression); unruffled; unconcerned\npure; upright; innocent" },
	{ "question": "深更", "answers": [ "しんこう" ], "comment": "middle of the night; dead of night; midnight" },
	{ "question": "混紡", "answers": [ "こんぼう" ], "comment": "mixed yarn; mixed spinning" },
	{ "question": "清艶", "answers": [ "せいえん" ] },
	{ "question": "渇望", "answers": [ "かつぼう" ], "comment": "craving; longing; thirsting" },
	{ "question": "渉外", "answers": [ "しょうがい" ], "comment": "public relations; client liaison; client relations" },
	{ "question": "渋滞", "answers": [ "じゅうたい" ], "comment": "congestion (e.g. traffic); delay; stagnation" },
	{ "question": "渓流", "answers": [ "けいりゅう" ], "comment": "mountain stream; mountain torrent" },
	{ "question": "渦潮", "answers": [ "うずしお" ], "comment": "whirling tides" },
	{ "question": "湧出", "answers": [ "ゆうしゅつ" ], "comment": "gushing out; welling up; springing up" },
	{ "question": "湧水", "answers": [ "ゆうすい" ], "comment": "spring; welling of water" },
	{ "question": "溺れる", "answers": [ "おぼれる" ], "comment": "to drown; to nearly drown; to sink below the surface (of water)\nto indulge in; to lose one's head over something; to wallow in" },
	{ "question": "溺愛", "answers": [ "できあい" ], "comment": "doting" },
	{ "question": "溺死", "answers": [ "できし" ], "comment": "death by drowning" },
	{ "question": "滑稽", "answers": [ "こっけい" ], "comment": "funny; humorous; humourous; comical; laughable; ridiculous; joking" },
	{ "question": "滞り", "answers": [ "とどこおり" ], "comment": "stagnation; hindrance; delay" },
	{ "question": "漂う", "answers": [ "ただよう" ], "comment": "to drift; to float\nto waft (e.g. a scent); to hang in the air\nto be in the air (e.g. a feeling or mood)\nto wander; to walk around aimlessly\nto be unsteady; to be unstable\nto falter; to flinch; to wince\nto live in unreliable circumstances" },
	{ "question": "漆", "answers": [ "うるし" ], "comment": "seven\nhepta-\nlacquer; varnish; japan\nlacquer tree (Toxicodendron vernicifluum)" },
	{ "question": "漆器", "answers": [ "しっき" ], "comment": "lacquer ware; lacquerware; lacquer work; lacquerwork" },
	{ "question": "漏れる", "answers": [ "もれる" ], "comment": "to leak out; to escape; to come through; to shine through; to filter out\nto find expression; to give vent\nto leak out; to be divulged; to be disclosed\nto be omitted; to be left out; to be excluded; to be not included" },
	{ "question": "漠", "answers": [ "ばく" ], "comment": "vague; obscure; dim; indistinct; ambiguous" },
	{ "question": "漬物", "answers": [ "つけもの" ], "comment": "tsukemono; Japanese pickled vegetables" },
	{ "question": "漸増", "answers": [ "ぜんぞう" ], "comment": "gradual increase" },
	{ "question": "漸進", "answers": [ "ぜんしん" ], "comment": "gradual progress; steady advance" },
	{ "question": "潔く", "answers": [ "いさぎよく" ], "comment": "with (a) good grace; without reluctance; with no regret(s); once (and) for all\nwith resignation; resignedly" },
	{ "question": "潤す", "answers": [ "うるおす" ], "comment": "to moisten; to wet\nto profit; to enrich; to benefit" },
	{ "question": "潰す", "answers": [ "つぶす" ], "comment": "to smash; to crush\nto shut down\nto thwart; to block\nto kill (time)\nto waste (e.g. talents)" },
	{ "question": "潰れる", "answers": [ "つぶれる" ], "comment": "to be crushed; to be smashed; to be broken; to collapse\nto become useless; to cease functioning; to be wasted (e.g. time)\nto go bankrupt; to go out of business; to fail" },
	{ "question": "潰敗", "answers": [ "かいはい" ], "comment": "rout" },
	{ "question": "潰瘍", "answers": [ "かいよう" ], "comment": "ulcer" },
	{ "question": "潰走", "answers": [ "かいそう" ], "comment": "rout; stampede" },
	{ "question": "瀬戸際", "answers": [ "せとぎわ" ], "comment": "brink; critical moment" },
	{ "question": "火蓋", "answers": [ "ひぶた" ], "comment": "apron of a gun; cover for the touch-hole on a cannon or matchlock" },
	{ "question": "灯籠", "answers": [ "とうろう" ], "comment": "garden lantern; hanging lantern" },
	{ "question": "焦がす", "answers": [ "こがす" ], "comment": "to burn; to scorch; to singe; to char" },
	{ "question": "焦眉", "answers": [ "しょうび" ], "comment": "emergency; urgency; imminence" },
	{ "question": "焼酎", "answers": [ "しょうちゅう" ], "comment": "shochu; Japanese spirit distilled from sweet potatoes, rice, etc." },
	{ "question": "煎る", "answers": [ "いる" ], "comment": "to parch; to fry; to fire; to broil; to roast; to boil down (in oil)" },
	{ "question": "煎茶", "answers": [ "せんちゃ" ], "comment": "green tea; green leaf tea; non-powdered tea (as opposed to matcha)\nmedium-grade green tea" },
	{ "question": "煎餅", "answers": [ "せんべい" ], "comment": "rice cracker; Japanese cracker; rice cookie; wafer" },
	{ "question": "煮沸", "answers": [ "しゃふつ" ], "comment": "boiling up" },
	{ "question": "熊", "answers": [ "くま" ], "comment": "bear (any mammal of family Ursidae)" },
	{ "question": "爪先", "answers": [ "つまさき" ], "comment": "toes; tips of the toes; toe of a shoe, sock, etc." },
	{ "question": "爪弾き", "answers": [ "つまはじき" ], "comment": "black sheep (of a family); ostracism\nplaying with one's fingers (a guitar, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "爪牙", "answers": [ "そうが" ], "comment": "claws and fangs; claws and tusks\nclutches; devious design; means of causing harm; weapon\npawn; stooge; cat's-paw\nright-hand man" },
	{ "question": "爪痕", "answers": [ "つめあと" ], "comment": "fingernail mark; scratch\nscar; ravages; after-effects" },
	{ "question": "爽やか", "answers": [ "さわやか" ], "comment": "fresh; refreshing; invigorating\nclear (e.g. voice); fluent; eloquent" },
	{ "question": "爽快", "answers": [ "そうかい" ], "comment": "refreshing; exhilarating" },
	{ "question": "爽昧", "answers": [ "そうまい" ] },
	{ "question": "爽涼", "answers": [ "そうりょう" ], "comment": "cool and refreshing" },
	{ "question": "片隅", "answers": [ "かたすみ" ], "comment": "corner; nook" },
	{ "question": "牙", "answers": [ "きば" ], "comment": "tusk; fang" },
	{ "question": "牙城", "answers": [ "がじょう" ], "comment": "stronghold (esp. of an enemy or opponent); inner citadel; bastion" },
	{ "question": "犬猿", "answers": [ "けんえん" ], "comment": "dogs and monkeys (esp. as an example of a bad relationship, like that between cats and dogs)" },
	{ "question": "狂奔", "answers": [ "きょうほん" ], "comment": "rushing around; running wild" },
	{ "question": "狙撃", "answers": [ "そげき" ], "comment": "shooting; sniping" },
	{ "question": "狭義", "answers": [ "きょうぎ" ], "comment": "narrow sense (e.g. of a word); strict" },
	{ "question": "猛者", "answers": [ "もさ" ], "comment": "man of valour; man of valor; stalwart; tough guy; warrior" },
	{ "question": "玩味", "answers": [ "がんみ" ], "comment": "relish; appreciation" },
	{ "question": "玩読", "answers": [ "がんどく" ] },
	{ "question": "珠玉", "answers": [ "しゅぎょく" ], "comment": "gem; jewel\nbeautiful; accomplished; charming" },
	{ "question": "珠算", "answers": [ "しゅざん" ], "comment": "calculation with abacus" },
	{ "question": "瓦石", "answers": [ "がせき" ], "comment": "worthless thing; garbage; roof tile and stone\nbrick" },
	{ "question": "瓦解", "answers": [ "がかい" ], "comment": "collapse; downfall" },
	{ "question": "甚だしい", "answers": [ "はなはだしい" ], "comment": "extreme; excessive; terrible; intense; severe; serious; tremendous; heavy (damage)" },
	{ "question": "甚大", "answers": [ "じんだい" ], "comment": "very great; enormous; serious" },
	{ "question": "生涯", "answers": [ "しょうがい" ], "comment": "one's lifetime (i.e. one's existence until death); one's career" },
	{ "question": "産着", "answers": [ "うぶぎ" ], "comment": "clothes for a newborn baby; baby clothes" },
	{ "question": "由", "answers": [ "よし" ], "comment": "reason; significance; cause\npiece of information that one has heard; I hear that ...; it is said that ..." },
	{ "question": "由緒", "answers": [ "ゆいしょ" ], "comment": "history; pedigree; lineage" },
	{ "question": "畏怖", "answers": [ "いふ" ], "comment": "awe; fear; fright" },
	{ "question": "畏敬", "answers": [ "いけい" ], "comment": "reverence; awe; respect" },
	{ "question": "畏縮", "answers": [ "いしゅく" ], "comment": "wince; cower; recoil" },
	{ "question": "疎い", "answers": [ "うとい" ], "comment": "distant; estranged; disinterested\npoorly informed; unfamiliar; ignorant" },
	{ "question": "疎遠", "answers": [ "そえん" ], "comment": "estrangement; neglect; silence" },
	{ "question": "疑惧", "answers": [ "ぎぐ" ], "comment": "apprehension; uneasiness" },
	{ "question": "痕跡", "answers": [ "こんせき" ], "comment": "trace; traces; vestige; vestiges" },
	{ "question": "痩せる", "answers": [ "やせる" ], "comment": "to become thin; to lose weight; to reduce (one's) weight; to slim\nto be barren; to be infertile; to be sterile" },
	{ "question": "痩地", "answers": [ "そうち" ] },
	{ "question": "痩身", "answers": [ "そうしん" ], "comment": "slim figure; lean figure\nweight reduction" },
	{ "question": "盆栽", "answers": [ "ぼんさい" ], "comment": "bonsai; miniature potted plant" },
	{ "question": "目尻", "answers": [ "めじり" ], "comment": "outer canthus; outer corner of the eye" },
	{ "question": "盲亀", "answers": [ "もうき" ], "comment": "blind turtle" },
	{ "question": "眉唾物", "answers": [ "まゆつばもの" ], "comment": "fake; counterfeit" },
	{ "question": "眉間", "answers": [ "みけん" ], "comment": "brow; glabella; middle forehead; area between the eyebrows" },
	{ "question": "真摯", "answers": [ "しんし" ], "comment": "sincere; earnest" },
	{ "question": "眺め", "answers": [ "ながめ" ], "comment": "scene; view; prospect; outlook" },
	{ "question": "眺める", "answers": [ "ながめる" ], "comment": "to view; to gaze at" },
	{ "question": "眺望", "answers": [ "ちょうぼう" ], "comment": "prospect; view; outlook" },
	{ "question": "督促", "answers": [ "とくそく" ], "comment": "urge; demand; importunity" },
	{ "question": "瞳孔", "answers": [ "どうこう" ], "comment": "pupil; pupillary" },
	{ "question": "砂利", "answers": [ "じゃり" ], "comment": "gravel; ballast; pebbles\nchild; rugrat; ankle-biter" },
	{ "question": "砂嵐", "answers": [ "すなあらし" ], "comment": "sandstorm\nnoise (video); snow" },
	{ "question": "砕ける", "answers": [ "くだける" ], "comment": "to break (into pieces); to be broken; to be smashed\nto collapse; to crumble; to decline; to cool (e.g. enthusiasm); to dampen (e.g. one's will to fight)\nto become less formal; to throw off reserve; to become affable\nto become easy to understand (e.g. a story)\nto be worried" },
	{ "question": "砕石", "answers": [ "さいせき" ], "comment": "broken stone; rubble" },
	{ "question": "破綻", "answers": [ "はたん" ], "comment": "failure; bankruptcy" },
	{ "question": "磨く", "answers": [ "みがく" ], "comment": "to polish; to shine; to brush (e.g. teeth)\nto refine; to improve" },
	{ "question": "磨耗", "answers": [ "まもう" ], "comment": "wear; abrasion" },
	{ "question": "礎", "answers": [ "いしずえ" ], "comment": "foundation stone; cornerstone" },
	{ "question": "示唆", "answers": [ "しさ" ], "comment": "suggestion; hint; implication" },
	{ "question": "禁錮", "answers": [ "きんこ" ], "comment": "imprisonment; confinement" },
	{ "question": "禁錮刑", "answers": [ "きんこけい" ], "comment": "(penalty of) imprisonment" },
	{ "question": "稚拙", "answers": [ "ちせつ" ], "comment": "unskillful; childish; immature; naive; artless; clumsy; crude" },
	{ "question": "種苗", "answers": [ "しゅびょう" ], "comment": "seeds and seedlings; eggs and hatchlings; (fish) eggs and fry" },
	{ "question": "稼働", "answers": [ "かどう" ], "comment": "operation (of machine); operating; running; working" },
	{ "question": "稼動", "answers": [ "かどう" ], "comment": "operation (of machine); operating; running; working" },
	{ "question": "稽古", "answers": [ "けいこ" ], "comment": "practice; practising; training; study" },
	{ "question": "穏やか", "answers": [ "おだやか" ], "comment": "calm; gentle; quiet" },
	{ "question": "空隙", "answers": [ "くうげき" ], "comment": "vacant space; aperture; gap; opening" },
	{ "question": "窮める", "answers": [ "きわめる" ], "comment": "to carry to extremes; to go to the end of something\nto investigate thoroughly; to master" },
	{ "question": "窮地", "answers": [ "きゅうち" ], "comment": "dilemma; predicament" },
	{ "question": "窮状", "answers": [ "きゅうじょう" ], "comment": "distress; wretched condition" },
	{ "question": "窯元", "answers": [ "かまもと" ], "comment": "pottery (i.e. the place)\npotter" },
	{ "question": "竜巻", "answers": [ "たつまき" ], "comment": "tornado; waterspout" },
	{ "question": "童歌", "answers": [ "わらべうた" ], "comment": "children's song; nursery song" },
	{ "question": "端数", "answers": [ "はすう" ], "comment": "fraction; odd amount; leftover amount" },
	{ "question": "競う", "answers": [ "きそう" ], "comment": "to compete with\nto emulate" },
	{ "question": "競り", "answers": [ "せり" ], "comment": "competing; competition\nauction" },
	{ "question": "竹串", "answers": [ "たけぐし" ], "comment": "bamboo skewer" },
	{ "question": "筒先", "answers": [ "つつさき" ], "comment": "nozzle; muzzle; gunpoint" },
	{ "question": "筒抜け", "answers": [ "つつぬけ" ], "comment": "being overheard; being leaked (e.g. secrets)\ngoing in one ear and out the other" },
	{ "question": "箸", "answers": [ "はし" ], "comment": "chopsticks" },
	{ "question": "籠城", "answers": [ "ろうじょう" ], "comment": "holding a castle (during a siege); holing up\nconfinement (to one's home); staying at home; staying indoors" },
	{ "question": "籠絡", "answers": [ "ろうらく" ], "comment": "inveigling; ensnaring; enticement; cajoling" },
	{ "question": "粛然", "answers": [ "しゅくぜん" ], "comment": "silent; quiet; solemn\nsoftly; quietly; solemnly" },
	{ "question": "精緻", "answers": [ "せいち" ], "comment": "delicate; minute; subtle" },
	{ "question": "納屋", "answers": [ "なや" ], "comment": "shed; barn; outhouse" },
	{ "question": "紙幣", "answers": [ "しへい" ], "comment": "paper money; note; bill" },
	{ "question": "紡ぐ", "answers": [ "つむぐ" ], "comment": "to spin; to make yarn\nto spin (a tale); to speak" },
	{ "question": "索引", "answers": [ "さくいん" ], "comment": "index; indices; indexes" },
	{ "question": "累計", "answers": [ "るいけい" ], "comment": "cumulative total; accumulated total; total up to now" },
	{ "question": "絞る", "answers": [ "しぼる" ], "comment": "to wring (towel, rag); to squeeze\nto squeeze (fruit to extract juice); to press; to extract; to milk; to express milk\nto rack (one's brains); to strain (one's voice)\nto extort; to exploit\nto chew out; to reprimand severely; to rake over the coals; to give a sound scolding; to tell someone off; to scold; to rebuke\nto drill into; to train\nto narrow down (one's focus); to whittle down\nto gather up (curtain, etc.); to tighten (drawstring)\nto stop down (lens)\nto turn down (e.g. radio)\nto bend (bow); to draw\nto hold down; to constrict; to immobilize" },
	{ "question": "絡む", "answers": [ "からむ" ], "comment": "to entangle; to entwine\nto pick a quarrel; to find fault\nto be involved with; to be influenced by; to develop a connection with" },
	{ "question": "絶叫", "answers": [ "ぜっきょう" ], "comment": "scream; shriek; shout; exclamation" },
	{ "question": "絶崖", "answers": [ "ぜつがい" ] },
	{ "question": "維持", "answers": [ "いじ" ], "comment": "maintenance; preservation; improvement" },
	{ "question": "綻びる", "answers": [ "ほころびる" ], "comment": "to come apart at the seams; to be ripped; to be torn\nto begin to open; to begin to bloom\nto smile broadly; to break into a smile" },
	{ "question": "緑青", "answers": [ "ろくしょう" ], "comment": "verdigris; green rust; copper rust" },
	{ "question": "緩和", "answers": [ "かんわ" ], "comment": "relief; mitigation; alleviation; relaxation; softening" },
	{ "question": "緻密", "answers": [ "ちみつ" ], "comment": "minute; fine; delicate; accurate; precise; elaborate" },
	{ "question": "罪業", "answers": [ "ざいごう" ], "comment": "sin; iniquity; crime" },
	{ "question": "罵る", "answers": [ "ののしる" ], "comment": "to abuse (verbally); to curse at; to shout abuse at; to speak ill of" },
	{ "question": "罵倒", "answers": [ "ばとう" ], "comment": "abuse; disparagement" },
	{ "question": "罵声", "answers": [ "ばせい" ], "comment": "boos; jeers" },
	{ "question": "罵言", "answers": [ "ばげん" ], "comment": "abuse" },
	{ "question": "罷免", "answers": [ "ひめん" ], "comment": "dismissal; discharge" },
	{ "question": "美貌", "answers": [ "びぼう" ], "comment": "beautiful face; good looks; beauty" },
	{ "question": "羞恥", "answers": [ "しゅうち" ], "comment": "shyness; bashfulness; shame" },
	{ "question": "羞悪", "answers": [ "しゅうお" ], "comment": "shame and hatred of evil" },
	{ "question": "羨ましい", "answers": [ "うらやましい" ], "comment": "envious (feeling, etc.); jealous\nenviable (position, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "羨む", "answers": [ "うらやむ" ], "comment": "to envy" },
	{ "question": "羨望", "answers": [ "せんぼう" ], "comment": "envy" },
	{ "question": "翻弄", "answers": [ "ほんろう" ], "comment": "trifling with; toying with; playing with; making sport of; making fun of; leading around by the nose\ntossing about (a ship)" },
	{ "question": "聴聞", "answers": [ "ちょうもん" ], "comment": "listening; hearing" },
	{ "question": "肌身離さず", "answers": [ "はだみはなさず" ], "comment": "(carrying) close to one's person; next to the skin" },
	{ "question": "肘", "answers": [ "ひじ" ], "comment": "elbow" },
	{ "question": "肝腎", "answers": [ "かんじん" ], "comment": "essential; fundamental; crucial; vital; main" },
	{ "question": "股関節", "answers": [ "こかんせつ" ], "comment": "hip joint; coxa" },
	{ "question": "肥沃", "answers": [ "ひよく" ], "comment": "fertile; rich; productive" },
	{ "question": "肯定", "answers": [ "こうてい" ], "comment": "positive; affirmation" },
	{ "question": "胸臆", "answers": [ "きょうおく" ], "comment": "one's inmost thoughts (feelings)" },
	{ "question": "脅かす", "answers": [ "おどかす", "おびやかす" ], "comment": "to threaten; to menace\nto startle; to surprise\nto intimidate; to scare\nto jeopardize; to endanger; to imperil" },
	{ "question": "脅嚇", "answers": [ "きょうかく" ], "comment": "intimidation; threat" },
	{ "question": "脇腹", "answers": [ "わきばら" ], "comment": "side; flank\nillegitimate child; child born by someone other than one's wife" },
	{ "question": "脊柱", "answers": [ "せきちゅう" ], "comment": "spinal column" },
	{ "question": "脊椎", "answers": [ "せきつい" ], "comment": "spine; vertebral column" },
	{ "question": "脊髄", "answers": [ "せきずい" ], "comment": "spinal cord" },
	{ "question": "脚立", "answers": [ "きゃたつ" ], "comment": "stepladder; steps" },
	{ "question": "脱柵", "answers": [ "だっさく" ], "comment": "to escape its enclosure\nto desert from barracks; to break barracks" },
	{ "question": "脱臼", "answers": [ "だっきゅう" ], "comment": "dislocation" },
	{ "question": "腫れる", "answers": [ "はれる" ], "comment": "to swell (from inflammation); to become swollen" },
	{ "question": "腫瘍", "answers": [ "しゅよう" ], "comment": "tumor; tumour; neoplasm; neoplasia" },
	{ "question": "腺毛", "answers": [ "せんもう" ], "comment": "glandular hair" },
	{ "question": "膝", "answers": [ "ひざ" ], "comment": "knee\nlap; knee and thigh (while sitting)" },
	{ "question": "臆する", "answers": [ "おくする" ], "comment": "to be hesitant; to feel timid" },
	{ "question": "臆断", "answers": [ "おくだん" ], "comment": "jumping to hasty conclusions; conjecture" },
	{ "question": "臆面", "answers": [ "おくめん" ], "comment": "shy face" },
	{ "question": "自嘲", "answers": [ "じちょう" ], "comment": "self-deprecation; self-derision; self-mockery; laughing at oneself" },
	{ "question": "臼", "answers": [ "うす" ], "comment": "millstone; mortar" },
	{ "question": "舌禍", "answers": [ "ぜっか" ], "comment": "slip of tongue" },
	{ "question": "色艶", "answers": [ "いろつや" ], "comment": "colour and lustre; color and luster; complexion; colour; color" },
	{ "question": "芳しくない", "answers": [ "かんばしくない" ], "comment": "poor; unfavourable; unfavorable; disgraceful" },
	{ "question": "苛性", "answers": [ "かせい" ], "comment": "caustic" },
	{ "question": "苛烈", "answers": [ "かれつ" ], "comment": "severe; stern" },
	{ "question": "苛辣", "answers": [ "からつ" ] },
	{ "question": "苛酷", "answers": [ "かこく" ], "comment": "severe; harsh; hard; cruel; rigorous" },
	{ "question": "茎", "answers": [ "くき" ], "comment": "stalk; stem\ncore\ntang (of a sword, etc.)\nmiddle of a nest of boxes" },
	{ "question": "茨", "answers": [ "いばら" ], "comment": "thorny shrub\nwild rose; briar\nthorn\ncusp" },
	{ "question": "茨城県", "answers": [ "いばらきけん" ], "comment": "Ibaraki prefecture" },
	{ "question": "荘重", "answers": [ "そうちょう" ], "comment": "solemn; grave; impressive" },
	{ "question": "萎える", "answers": [ "なえる" ], "comment": "to lose strength; to become weak; to waste away\nto wither; to droop" },
	{ "question": "萎縮", "answers": [ "いしゅく" ], "comment": "withering; atrophy; contraction; dwarf" },
	{ "question": "葛切り", "answers": [ "くずきり" ], "comment": "kudzu starch noodles" },
	{ "question": "葛根湯", "answers": [ "かっこんとう" ], "comment": "infusion of kudzu, cinnamon, etc., used as an antifebrile, for hangovers, etc." },
	{ "question": "葛湯", "answers": [ "くずゆ" ], "comment": "kudzu starch gruel" },
	{ "question": "葛藤", "answers": [ "かっとう" ], "comment": "conflict; complication; troubles; discord\nChinese moonseed (Sinomenium acutum)\ncomplex inter-relationship (as in the struggle between two types of vine over one piece of land)" },
	{ "question": "葬る", "answers": [ "ほうむる" ], "comment": "to bury; to inter; to entomb\nto cover up; to hush up; to shelve" },
	{ "question": "蓋然", "answers": [ "がいぜん" ], "comment": "probability" },
	{ "question": "蔑む", "answers": [ "さげすむ" ], "comment": "to scorn; to despise; to hold in contempt; to look down on; to disdain" },
	{ "question": "蔑視", "answers": [ "べっし" ], "comment": "contempt; derision; slight; disdain" },
	{ "question": "薦める", "answers": [ "すすめる" ], "comment": "to recommend; to advise; to encourage; to offer (wine)" },
	{ "question": "薫陶", "answers": [ "くんとう" ], "comment": "education; training; discipline" },
	{ "question": "藍染め", "answers": [ "あいぞめ" ], "comment": "indigo dye" },
	{ "question": "藍色", "answers": [ "あいいろ", "らんしょく" ], "comment": "indigo blue" },
	{ "question": "虎口", "answers": [ "ここう" ], "comment": "tiger's den; jaws of death; dangerous place" },
	{ "question": "虎威", "answers": [ "こい" ] },
	{ "question": "虐げる", "answers": [ "しいたげる" ], "comment": "to oppress; to persecute; to tyrannize" },
	{ "question": "虚空", "answers": [ "こくう" ], "comment": "empty space; empty sky" },
	{ "question": "虹", "answers": [ "にじ" ], "comment": "rainbow" },
	{ "question": "蚊柱", "answers": [ "かばしら" ], "comment": "mosquito swarm" },
	{ "question": "蛇口", "answers": [ "じゃぐち" ], "comment": "faucet; tap" },
	{ "question": "蛍雪", "answers": [ "けいせつ" ], "comment": "diligence in studying (e.g. continuing to study even in such poor light as offered by a firefly or that reflected by snow); diligent study" },
	{ "question": "蜂起", "answers": [ "ほうき" ], "comment": "uprising; revolt" },
	{ "question": "蜜月", "answers": [ "みつげつ" ], "comment": "honeymoon\nin an intimate relationship" },
	{ "question": "血痕", "answers": [ "けっこん" ], "comment": "bloodstain" },
	{ "question": "衆寡", "answers": [ "しゅうか" ], "comment": "the many and the few" },
	{ "question": "行脚", "answers": [ "あんぎゃ" ], "comment": "pilgrimage; traveling on foot" },
	{ "question": "表彰", "answers": [ "ひょうしょう" ], "comment": "public acknowledgment; public acknowledgement; public recognition; commendation; awarding" },
	{ "question": "衰え", "answers": [ "おとろえ" ], "comment": "weakening; emaciation; decline" },
	{ "question": "衷心", "answers": [ "ちゅうしん" ], "comment": "innermost feelings" },
	{ "question": "裂ける", "answers": [ "さける" ], "comment": "to split; to tear; to burst" },
	{ "question": "装填", "answers": [ "そうてん" ], "comment": "loading; charging; filling" },
	{ "question": "補填", "answers": [ "ほてん" ], "comment": "compensating; making up for; supplementation" },
	{ "question": "製靴", "answers": [ "せいか" ], "comment": "shoe-making" },
	{ "question": "裾", "answers": [ "すそ" ], "comment": "hem; (trouser) cuff; shirttail\nbottom edge\nfoot (of a mountain)\ntips (of hair)\ndownstream" },
	{ "question": "褒める", "answers": [ "ほめる" ], "comment": "to praise; to admire; to speak well of someone" },
	{ "question": "要塞", "answers": [ "ようさい" ], "comment": "fort; stronghold; fortification" },
	{ "question": "覆す", "answers": [ "くつがえす" ], "comment": "to overturn; to capsize; to upset\nto overthrow (government etc.)\nto reverse (decision etc.); to disprove (an established theory etc.); to overrule" },
	{ "question": "親戚", "answers": [ "しんせき" ], "comment": "relative; relation; kin" },
	{ "question": "親睦", "answers": [ "しんぼく" ], "comment": "friendship; amity" },
	{ "question": "訃告", "answers": [ "ふこく" ], "comment": "death report" },
	{ "question": "訃報", "answers": [ "ふほう" ], "comment": "news of a person's death; obituary" },
	{ "question": "診察", "answers": [ "しんさつ" ], "comment": "medical examination" },
	{ "question": "詐欺", "answers": [ "さぎ" ], "comment": "fraud; swindle; graft; cheating; trick; scam" },
	{ "question": "詐称", "answers": [ "さしょう" ], "comment": "misrepresentation; false statement" },
	{ "question": "詣でる", "answers": [ "もうでる" ], "comment": "to make a pilgrimage" },
	{ "question": "詩吟", "answers": [ "しぎん" ], "comment": "reciting Chinese poems" },
	{ "question": "詮索", "answers": [ "せんさく" ], "comment": "inquiry into; enquiry into; prying (into); investigation; search; exploration" },
	{ "question": "詮議", "answers": [ "せんぎ" ], "comment": "discussion; examination\ninvestigation (of a criminal); questioning" },
	{ "question": "誇大", "answers": [ "こだい" ], "comment": "exaggeration; hyperbole" },
	{ "question": "誓約書", "answers": [ "せいやくしょ" ], "comment": "written oath; covenant; pledge" },
	{ "question": "語呂", "answers": [ "ごろ" ], "comment": "sound (of a sentence); euphony" },
	{ "question": "語彙", "answers": [ "ごい" ], "comment": "vocabulary; lexicon; lexis; terminology" },
	{ "question": "諦め", "answers": [ "あきらめ" ], "comment": "resignation; acceptance; consolation" },
	{ "question": "諦める", "answers": [ "あきらめる" ], "comment": "to give up; to abandon (hope, plans); to resign oneself (to)" },
	{ "question": "諦念", "answers": [ "ていねん" ], "comment": "understanding and acceptance; spiritual awakening; a heart that understands truth; (feeling of) resignation" },
	{ "question": "諦聴", "answers": [ "ていちょう" ] },
	{ "question": "諦視", "answers": [ "ていし" ] },
	{ "question": "諦観", "answers": [ "ていかん" ], "comment": "clear vision; resignation (as in reconciling oneself)" },
	{ "question": "諧和", "answers": [ "かいわ" ], "comment": "gentle mutual affection; harmony\nharmony" },
	{ "question": "謎めいた", "answers": [ "なぞめいた" ], "comment": "puzzling; enigmatic; mysterious; steeped in mystery" },
	{ "question": "謙虚", "answers": [ "けんきょ" ], "comment": "modesty; humility" },
	{ "question": "謙遜", "answers": [ "けんそん" ], "comment": "modesty; humility; being humble" },
	{ "question": "譲渡", "answers": [ "じょうと" ], "comment": "transfer; assignment; conveyance" },
	{ "question": "豊沃", "answers": [ "ほうよく" ], "comment": "fertility" },
	{ "question": "象牙", "answers": [ "ぞうげ" ], "comment": "ivory" },
	{ "question": "貝塚", "answers": [ "かいづか" ], "comment": "shell heap; shell mound; kitchen midden" },
	{ "question": "貢ぐ", "answers": [ "みつぐ" ], "comment": "to support (someone) financially; to finance; to supply (money); to give (in support)\nto present (money or gifts) to a monarch" },
	{ "question": "貪る", "answers": [ "むさぼる" ], "comment": "to covet; to crave; to lust insatiably for\nto indulge in; to devour greedily" },
	{ "question": "貪欲", "answers": [ "どんよく" ], "comment": "avarice; greed; covetousness\nraga (desire)" },
	{ "question": "貫く", "answers": [ "つらぬく" ], "comment": "to go through; to pierce; to penetrate\nto carry out; to persist; to keep (faith); to stick to (principles); to maintain (independence)" },
	{ "question": "貼る", "answers": [ "はる" ], "comment": "to stick; to paste; to affix\nto stretch; to spread; to strain; to tighten; to put up (tent)\nto form (e.g. ice on a pond)\nto fill; to swell\nto stick out; to put; to slap\nto be expensive\nto keep a watch on; to be on the lookout\nto span; to generate" },
	{ "question": "貼付", "answers": [ "ちょうふ" ], "comment": "pasting; sticking; attaching; affixing; appending" },
	{ "question": "貼用", "answers": [ "ちょうよう" ], "comment": "pasting; affixing" },
	{ "question": "賄う", "answers": [ "まかなう" ], "comment": "to give board to; to provide meals; to pay; to cover (the cost)" },
	{ "question": "賄賂", "answers": [ "わいろ" ], "comment": "bribe; sweetener; douceur" },
	{ "question": "賢い", "answers": [ "かしこい" ], "comment": "wise; clever; smart" },
	{ "question": "賭ける", "answers": [ "かける" ], "comment": "to wager; to bet; to risk; to stake; to gamble" },
	{ "question": "賭け事", "answers": [ "かけごと" ], "comment": "betting; gambling" },
	{ "question": "賭博", "answers": [ "とばく" ], "comment": "gambling" },
	{ "question": "賭場", "answers": [ "とば" ], "comment": "gambling den" },
	{ "question": "足袋", "answers": [ "たび" ], "comment": "tabi; Japanese socks (with split toe)" },
	{ "question": "踪跡", "answers": [ "そうせき" ], "comment": "one's traces; one's tracks\none's whereabouts" },
	{ "question": "軌跡", "answers": [ "きせき" ], "comment": "tire track\ntraces of a person or thing; path one has taken\nlocus" },
	{ "question": "軟体動物", "answers": [ "なんたいどうぶつ" ], "comment": "mollusc; mollusk" },
	{ "question": "軽蔑", "answers": [ "けいべつ" ], "comment": "scorn; disdain; contempt" },
	{ "question": "辛辣", "answers": [ "しんらつ" ], "comment": "bitter; sharp; acrimonious" },
	{ "question": "辣腕", "answers": [ "らつわん" ], "comment": "shrewdness; tact" },
	{ "question": "迅速", "answers": [ "じんそく" ], "comment": "quick; fast; rapid; swift; prompt; streamlined; expedited; expeditious" },
	{ "question": "近畿", "answers": [ "きんき" ], "comment": "Kinki (region around Osaka, Kyoto, Nara)" },
	{ "question": "逐一", "answers": [ "ちくいち" ], "comment": "one by one; in detail; minutely" },
	{ "question": "逓減", "answers": [ "ていげん" ], "comment": "gradual decrease; gradual diminution" },
	{ "question": "造詣", "answers": [ "ぞうけい" ], "comment": "deep knowledge; attainments; scholarship" },
	{ "question": "進捗", "answers": [ "しんちょく" ], "comment": "progress; being under way" },
	{ "question": "遊山", "answers": [ "ゆさん" ], "comment": "excursion; outing; picnic" },
	{ "question": "過酷", "answers": [ "かこく" ], "comment": "severe; harsh; hard; cruel; rigorous" },
	{ "question": "遜色", "answers": [ "そんしょく" ], "comment": "inferiority" },
	{ "question": "遡る", "answers": [ "さかのぼる" ], "comment": "to go upstream\nto go back (in time, to origin); to date back to; to trace back to; to make retroactive" },
	{ "question": "遡上", "answers": [ "そじょう" ], "comment": "going upstream; retroact; retrospect" },
	{ "question": "遡及", "answers": [ "そきゅう" ], "comment": "tracing back; retroactivity" },
	{ "question": "遭難", "answers": [ "そうなん" ], "comment": "disaster; shipwreck; accident; being stranded" },
	{ "question": "遮る", "answers": [ "さえぎる" ], "comment": "to interrupt; to obstruct (e.g. a view, someone's way); to block (e.g. light, wind); to intercept" },
	{ "question": "遮蔽", "answers": [ "しゃへい" ], "comment": "shielding; sheltering; screening; shading; masking" },
	{ "question": "選択肢", "answers": [ "せんたくし" ], "comment": "choices; alternatives; options" },
	{ "question": "還暦", "answers": [ "かんれき" ], "comment": "60th birthday" },
	{ "question": "邪魔", "answers": [ "じゃま" ], "comment": "hindrance; obstacle; nuisance\nto visit (somebody's home)\ndemon who hinders Buddhist training; demon who obstructs sentient beings from maintaining moral behaviour" },
	{ "question": "配膳", "answers": [ "はいぜん" ], "comment": "setting a place; setting the table" },
	{ "question": "酪農", "answers": [ "らくのう" ], "comment": "dairy (farm)" },
	{ "question": "酷評", "answers": [ "こくひょう" ], "comment": "severe criticism; damnation" },
	{ "question": "醜い", "answers": [ "みにくい" ], "comment": "ugly; unattractive\nunsightly; unseemly" },
	{ "question": "醜悪", "answers": [ "しゅうあく" ], "comment": "ugliness; meanness; offensiveness" },
	{ "question": "醜聞", "answers": [ "しゅうぶん" ], "comment": "scandal" },
	{ "question": "醸す", "answers": [ "かもす" ], "comment": "to brew (sake, etc.)\nto cause; to bring on; to bring about; to give rise to" },
	{ "question": "采配", "answers": [ "さいはい" ], "comment": "baton (of command)\norder; command; direction" },
	{ "question": "釜飯", "answers": [ "かまめし" ], "comment": "rice, meat and vegetable dish served in a small pot" },
	{ "question": "釣果", "answers": [ "ちょうか" ], "comment": "catch (fishing); amount of fish caught; caught fish" },
	{ "question": "鉄柵", "answers": [ "てっさく" ], "comment": "iron railing or fence" },
	{ "question": "錦", "answers": [ "にしき" ], "comment": "brocade\nfine dress; fine clothes" },
	{ "question": "錦秋", "answers": [ "きんしゅう" ], "comment": "autumn where the foliage is as beautiful as brocade; autumn with beautiful leaves" },
	{ "question": "錦衣", "answers": [ "きんい" ] },
	{ "question": "鍛える", "answers": [ "きたえる" ], "comment": "to forge; to temper\nto drill; to train; to discipline" },
	{ "question": "鍵盤", "answers": [ "けんばん" ], "comment": "keyboard (e.g. piano, computer)" },
	{ "question": "鍵穴", "answers": [ "かぎあな" ], "comment": "keyhole" },
	{ "question": "鎌", "answers": [ "かま" ], "comment": "sickle\nsickle-and-chain (weapon)\nspear with curved cross-blades\ngooseneck tenon and mortise joint\nnoisiness\npart of a fish around the gills" },
	{ "question": "鎌首", "answers": [ "かまくび" ], "comment": "sickle-shaped neck (e.g. snake, praying mantis); crooked neck; gooseneck" },
	{ "question": "鎮める", "answers": [ "しずめる" ], "comment": "to appease; to suppress; to calm" },
	{ "question": "鏡餅", "answers": [ "かがみもち" ], "comment": "mirror-shaped mochi, usu. a pair stacked in order of size with a daidai on top, used as a New Year offering, then cut and eaten on January 11." },
	{ "question": "長患い", "answers": [ "ながわずらい" ], "comment": "long illness; protracted illness" },
	{ "question": "閉塞", "answers": [ "へいそく" ], "comment": "closure; blockage" },
	{ "question": "開襟", "answers": [ "かいきん" ], "comment": "open-necked (shirt)" },
	{ "question": "閑却", "answers": [ "かんきゃく" ], "comment": "negligence; disregard" },
	{ "question": "間隙", "answers": [ "かんげき" ], "comment": "gap" },
	{ "question": "闇夜", "answers": [ "やみよ" ], "comment": "dark night\ndark night" },
	{ "question": "附記", "answers": [ "ふき" ], "comment": "addition; appendix; note; supplement" },
	{ "question": "陥る", "answers": [ "おちいる" ], "comment": "to fall into (e.g. a hole)\nto fall into (chaos, depression, dilemma, illness, etc.)\nto fall into (a trap, etc.)\nto fall; to surrender; to capitulate" },
	{ "question": "陥れる", "answers": [ "おとしいれる" ], "comment": "to trick someone into (committing a crime, etc.); to hatch a plan and deceive someone\nto assault (a castle, etc.)\nto drop something and have it fall into something" },
	{ "question": "陳謝", "answers": [ "ちんしゃ" ], "comment": "apology" },
	{ "question": "陶冶", "answers": [ "とうや" ], "comment": "training; education; cultivation" },
	{ "question": "隔離", "answers": [ "かくり" ], "comment": "isolation; segregation; separation; quarantine" },
	{ "question": "隙", "answers": [ "すき" ], "comment": "gap; space\nbreak; interlude; interval\nchink (in one's armor, armour); chance; opportunity; weak spot\nbreach (of a relationship between people)" },
	{ "question": "隠蔽", "answers": [ "いんぺい" ], "comment": "concealment; suppression; hiding" },
	{ "question": "雑巾", "answers": [ "ぞうきん" ], "comment": "house-cloth; dust cloth" },
	{ "question": "雪崩", "answers": [ "なだれ" ], "comment": "avalanche; snowslide" },
	{ "question": "雪渓", "answers": [ "せっけい" ], "comment": "snowy valley" },
	{ "question": "雪辱", "answers": [ "せつじょく" ], "comment": "vindication of honour; vindication of honor; making up for loss; revenge" },
	{ "question": "雰囲気", "answers": [ "ふんいき" ], "comment": "mood; ambience; ambiance; aura; feel\na certain air; presence; special aura; something (about someone)\nair; atmosphere" },
	{ "question": "霜害", "answers": [ "そうがい" ], "comment": "frost damage" },
	{ "question": "霜柱", "answers": [ "しもばしら" ], "comment": "frost columns; ice needles" },
	{ "question": "露呈", "answers": [ "ろてい" ], "comment": "exposure; disclosure" },
	{ "question": "静粛", "answers": [ "せいしゅく" ], "comment": "silent" },
	{ "question": "音頭", "answers": [ "おんど" ], "comment": "leading a group of people; someone who leads others into a song by singing the leading notes\nworkmen's songs; marching songs" },
	{ "question": "頂戴", "answers": [ "ちょうだい" ], "comment": "receiving; reception; getting; being given\neating; drinking; having\nplease; please do for me" },
	{ "question": "頃合い", "answers": [ "ころあい" ], "comment": "suitable time; good time\npropriety; moderation" },
	{ "question": "頑固", "answers": [ "がんこ" ], "comment": "stubborn; obstinate; pigheaded" },
	{ "question": "頒価", "answers": [ "はんか" ], "comment": "distribution price" },
	{ "question": "頒布", "answers": [ "はんぷ" ], "comment": "distribution" },
	{ "question": "頓挫", "answers": [ "とんざ" ], "comment": "setback; deadlock; being at a standstill or impasse" },
	{ "question": "頓知", "answers": [ "とんち" ], "comment": "quick wit; ready wit" },
	{ "question": "頬張る", "answers": [ "ほおばる" ], "comment": "to stuff one's cheeks; to fill one's mouth (with food)" },
	{ "question": "頬桁", "answers": [ "ほおげた" ], "comment": "cheekbone" },
	{ "question": "頻出", "answers": [ "ひんしゅつ" ], "comment": "common; frequent" },
	{ "question": "頻発", "answers": [ "ひんぱつ" ], "comment": "frequency; frequent occurrence" },
	{ "question": "顎", "answers": [ "あご" ], "comment": "chin; jaw\nchin; jaw\ngills; branchia" },
	{ "question": "顎関節", "answers": [ "がくかんせつ" ], "comment": "jaw joint; temporomandibular joint; TMJ" },
	{ "question": "顕示", "answers": [ "けんじ" ], "comment": "manifestation; public show; showing conspicuously" },
	{ "question": "顕著", "answers": [ "けんちょ" ], "comment": "remarkable; striking; obvious" },
	{ "question": "風貌", "answers": [ "ふうぼう" ], "comment": "looks; appearance" },
	{ "question": "風采", "answers": [ "ふうさい" ], "comment": "appearance; air; mien; getup" },
	{ "question": "養蜂場", "answers": [ "ようほうじょう" ], "comment": "bee yard; apiary" },
	{ "question": "餌食", "answers": [ "えじき" ], "comment": "prey; victim" },
	{ "question": "駒", "answers": [ "こま" ], "comment": "piece (in shogi, chess, etc.)\nhorse; foal\nbridge (of a violin, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "骸骨", "answers": [ "がいこつ" ], "comment": "skeleton" },
	{ "question": "高騰", "answers": [ "こうとう" ], "comment": "sudden price jump; steep price rise" },
	{ "question": "鬱乎", "answers": [ "うっこ" ] },
	{ "question": "鬱屈", "answers": [ "うっくつ" ], "comment": "gloomy" },
	{ "question": "鬱積", "answers": [ "うっせき" ], "comment": "accumulation (e.g. of emotions, grievances, etc.); buildup; suppression (e.g. of anger)" },
	{ "question": "鬱結", "answers": [ "うっけつ" ], "comment": "depression; oppression" },
	{ "question": "魂胆", "answers": [ "こんたん" ], "comment": "ulterior motive; plot; scheme\ncomplicated circumstances; intricacies" },
	{ "question": "魔窟", "answers": [ "まくつ" ], "comment": "den of thieves\nbrothel; red-light district\ncluttered room" },
	{ "question": "麓", "answers": [ "ふもと" ], "comment": "foot (of a mountain or hill); bottom; base" },
	{ "question": "麻酔", "answers": [ "ますい" ], "comment": "anaesthesia; anesthesia" },
	{ "question": "黒鍵", "answers": [ "こっけん" ], "comment": "black keys" }
]
}
